Christensen, C. Roland (Carl Roland), 1919-1999. C. Roland Christensen Papers, 1931-1998: A Finding Aid
C. Roland Christensen papers, 1931-1998
- II. HBS Teaching Records, 1931-1998
  - A. Annotated Cases, circa 1948-1990
    - Instruments, Inc., BP 446 (Box 20, f. 4)
    - Insulated Wire and Cable Co., BP 586 (Box 20, f. 5)
    - International Manufacturing Co., BP 779 (Box 20, f. 6)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (B1)(B2), BP 780r2 and BP 781 (Box 20, f. 7)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (C), BP 782 (Box 21, f. 1)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (D), BP 783 (Box 21, f. 2)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (E), BP 784 (Box 21, f. 3)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (F), BP 785 (Box 21, f. 4)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (G), BP 786r1 (Box 21, f. 5)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (H1)(H2), BP 787r1 and BP 788 (Box 21, f. 6)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (I), BP 789 (Box 21, f. 7)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (J), BP 869 (Box 21, f. 8)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (revisited), exam, 1966 (Box 21, f. 9)
    - International Manufacturing Co., teaching plan (Box 21, f. 10)
    - Itex Corporation (A), BP 917b (Box 21, f. 11)
    - Itex Corporation (B), BP 917b (Box 21, f. 12)
    - Itex Corporation (C), BP 918 (Box 21, f. 13)
    - Jacquier Watch Co., GM 8, IMEDE (Box 21, f. 14)
    - Jordan Chemicals, Inc. (A)(B), 0-382-168 and 0-382-169 (Box 22, f. 1)
    - Kaiser-Frazer Corporation, BP 428 (Box 22, f. 2)
    - Kampgrounds of America, Inc. (Box 22, f. 3)
    - Kassel, A.G., GM 109r1, IMEDE (Box 22, f. 4)
    - Kesler Manufacturing Co., BP 324 (Box 22, f. 5)
    - Klein System, Inc., BP 329 (Box 22, f. 6)
    - Knickerbocker Candy Co., BP 315 (Box 22, f. 7)
    - Kroger Grocery and Baking Co., BP 377 (Box 22, f. 8)
    - Lanfield, C.W., Co., BP 409 (Box 22, f. 9)
    - LaPlant-Choate Manufacturing Co., BP 435 (Box 22, f. 10)
    - The Larger Co. (A), EA-A 116 (Box 22, f. 11)
    - Lawlock Beverage Co., BP 301 (Box 22, f. 12)
    - Leisure Group, Inc. (A), 4-376-204 (Box 23, f. 1)
    - Leisure Group, Inc. (B), 4-376-205 (Box 23, f. 2)
    - Letters to a Business Policy Professor, 4-375-342 (Box 23, f. 3)
    - Lincoln Electric Co., 9-376-028 (Box 23, f. 4)
    - Linton Co., BP 582 (Box 23, f. 5)
    - Linton Co., BP 481 (Box 23, f. 6)
    - Linton Co. (B), BP 568 (Box 23, f. 7)
    - Litton Industries (Ar), AMP 262 (Box 23, f. 8)
    - Litton Industries (Br), AMP 263 (Box 23, f. 9)
    - Litton Industries (C), AMP 264 (Box 23, f. 10)
    - Lunt Scissors Corporation, BP 408 (Box 23, f. 11)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (AT), AMP 152 (Box 23, f. 12)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (BT), AMP 153 (Box 23, f. 13)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (CT), AMP 154 (Box 23, f. 14)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (DT), AMP 115 (Box 24, f. 1)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (RA), AMP 127 (Box 24, f. 2)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (RB), AMP 128 (Box 24, f. 3)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (RC), AMP 129 (Box 24, f. 4)
    - McGraw Hill, Inc. (RD), AMP 130 (Box 24, f. 5)
    - Management Succession and Board Membership, 9-380-132 (Box 24, f. 6)
    - Managers in the U.S. and Russia, BP 797 (Box 24, f. 7)
    - Mandell Supply Co., BP 422 (Box 24, f. 8)
    - Marks and Spencer, Ltd. (A), 1-375-358 (Box 24, f. 9)
    - Marlin Firearms Co., 4-371-186 (Box 24, f. 10)
    - Massey-Ferguson, Ltd., BP 866 (Box 24, f. 11)
    - Mathatronics, Inc., BP 815 (Box 24, f. 12)
    - Mead Corporation, 9-377-183 (Box 24, f. 13)
    - Medical Committee for Human Rights vs. SEC, 3-372-081 (Box 25, f. 1)
    - Merck and Co. (A), BP 493 (Box 25, f. 2)
    - Merck and Co. (Ar), BP 577 (Box 25, f. 3)
    - Merck and Co. (B), BP 494 (Box 25, f. 4)
    - Merck and Co. (Br), BP 578 (Box 25, f. 5)
    - Merck and Co. (Cr), BP 579 (Box 25, f. 6)
    - Merck and Co. (D), BP 661 (Box 25, f. 7)
    - Merlin Microwave, Inc., BP 974 (Box 25, f. 8)
    - Midway Foods Corporation, BP 662 (Box 25, f. 9)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (A), BP 649 (Box 25, f. 10)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (B1)(B2)(B3)(B4), BP 650-BP 653 (Box 25, f. 11)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (C), BP 654 (Box 25, f. 12)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (C2), BP 870 (Box 26, f. 1)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (D1)(D2)(D3), BP 655-BP 657 (Box 26, f. 2)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (E1)(E2), BP 658-BP 659 (Box 26, f. 3)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (F1)(F2)(F3)(F4)(F5) (Box 26, f. 4)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (G1)(G2)(G3) (Box 26, f. 5)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (H), BP 791 (Box 26, f. 6)
    - Midway Foods Corporation, outline # 3 (Box 26, f. 7)
    - Mr. Hart and Bing, HP 324 (Box 26, f. 8)
    - Mitchell, William (Box 26, f. 9)
    - Monarch Metal Products, BP 421 (Box 26, f. 10)
    - Mooney Aircraft, Inc., BP 935 (Box 26, f. 11)
    - “My Years with General Motors,” by Alfred Sloan, BP 856 (Box 26, f. 12)
    - Multi-Products, Inc., BP 643 (Box 26, f. 13)
    - National Cereal Distributors, BP 522 (Box 26, f. 14)
    - National Duplicating Products Corporation (A), BP 606 (Box 26, f. 15)
    - National Duplicating Products Corporation (B), BP 607 (Box 26, f. 16)
    - National Finance Co. (A), BP 473 (Box 27, f. 1)
    - National Finance Co. (B), BP 474r (Box 27, f. 2)
    - National Finance Co. (C), BP 475 (Box 27, f. 3)
    - National Finance Co. (D), BP 476 (Box 27, f. 4)
    - National Finance Co. (E), BP 477 (Box 27, f. 5)
    - National Finance Co. (F), BP 478 (Box 27, f. 6)
    - National Finance Co. (G), BP 496 (Box 27, f. 7)
    - National Finance Co. (H), BP 497 (Box 27, f. 8)
    - National Finance Co. (I), BP 675 (Box 27, f. 9)
    - National Finance Co. (J), BP 676 (Box 27, f. 10)
    - National Finance Co., cases, revised (Box 27, f. 11)
    - National Research Corporation, BP 426 (Box 27, f. 12)
    - NEFCO (A1)(A2), BP 713 and BP 714 (Box 27, f. 13)
    - NEFCO (Ar), BP 742r1, ICH 8G44r (Box 27, f. 14)
    - NEFCO (B)(B1)(B2)(B3)(B4)(B5)(B6)(B7), BP 715 - BP 722 (Box 28, f. 1-2)
    - NEFCO (Br), BP 743r1, ICH 8G45r (Box 28, f. 3)
    - NEFCO (C), BP 723 (Box 28, f. 4)
    - NEFCO (Cr), BP 744, ICH 8G46 (Box 28, f. 5)
    - Neubolt Tool Co., BP 354 (Box 28, f. 6)
    - New York Times, revised, BP 733 and BP 733r (Box 28, f. 7)
    - Northeastern Food Co. (A)(B), 4-372-153 (Box 28, f. 8)
    - Note on American Symphony Orchestras in the 1970s, 4-374-080 (Box 28, f. 9)
    - Note on Automobile Emissions and Fuel Economy Regulation (Box 28, f. 10)
    - Note on Corporate Boards of Directors, 4-372-309 (Box 28, f. 11)
    - Note on Light Aircraft Industry, revised, BP 932 (Box 28, f. 12)
    - Note on the Major Airplane Industry (Box 28, f. 13)
    - Note on the Mechanical Writing Instrument Industry, 4-374-341 (Box 29, f. 1)
    - Note on the Metal Container Industry, BP 799 (Box 29, f. 2)
    - Note on the Mobile Home Industry, 4-374-066 (Box 29, f. 3)
    - Note on the Mutual Fund Industry, 4-372-067 (Box 29, f. 4)
    - Note on the Newspaper Industry, 4-376-082 (Box 29, f. 5)
    - Note on the Security Services and Equipment Industry, 4-374-358 (Box 29, f. 6)
    - Note on the Soft Drink Industry, 377-213 (Box 29, f. 7-9)
    - Note on the Soft Drink Industry, 4-377-213 (Box 29, f. 10)
    - Note on the U.S. Bicycle Industry, 9-375-067 (Box 30, f. 1)
    - Note on the U.S. Chemical Industry (Box 30, f. 2)
    - “Notes on a Theory of Advice,” by L. Bryson, BP 984 (Box 30, f. 3)
    - Nowell, R.H., Co., BP 393 (Box 30, f. 4)
    - Of What Use Is a Board of Directors? BP 665 (Box 30, f. 5)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (A1), AMP 224 (Box 30, f. 6)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (A2), AMP 225 (Box 30, f. 7)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (A3), AMP 226 (Box 30, f. 8)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (A4), AMP 227r (Box 30, f. 9)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (A5), AMP 228 (Box 30, f. 10)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (A6), AMP 229 (Box 30, f. 11)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (B1), AMP 230 (Box 30, f. 12)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (B2), AMP 231 (Box 30, f. 13)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (C1), AMP 232 (Box 30, f. 14)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (C2), AMP 233 (Box 30, f. 15)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (D), AMP 234 (Box 30, f. 16)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (E1), AMP 235 (Box 30, f. 17)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (E2), AMP 236 (Box 30, f. 18)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (F1), AMP 237 (Box 30, f. 19)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (G1), AMP 245 (Box 31, f. 1)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (G2), AMP 264r (Box 31, f. 2)
    - Olivetti, C., and Co. (H), AMP 247 (Box 31, f. 3)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation, BP 430 (Box 31, f. 4)
    - Packard Motor Car Co., BP 480 (Box 31, f. 5)
    - Patterson and Swift, Inc., BP 575 (Box 31, f. 6)
    - Pearson Petroleum Co., BP 370 (Box 31, f. 7)
    - Pembroke Electric Co., BP 360 (Box 31, f. 8)
    - Personal Values, note on (Box 31, f. 9)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (A), EA-A 137 (Box 31, f. 10)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (A2), BP 617 (Box 31, f. 11)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (B), EA-A 138 (Box 31, f. 12)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (D1)(D2), EA-A 142 and EA-A 143 (Box 31, f. 13)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (D3), BP 619 (Box 31, f. 14)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (D4), BP 620 (Box 31, f. 15)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (D5), BP 621 (Box 31, f. 16)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (D6), BP 622 (Box 31, f. 17)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (E), EA-A 144 (Box 31, f. 18)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (F), EA-A 145 (Box 31, f. 19)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (G1)(G2), EA-A 146 and EA-A 147 (Box 31, f. 20)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (I1)(I2), EA-A 150 and EA-A 151 (Box 31, f. 21)
    - Petroleum Corporation of America (I3), BP 623 (Box 31, f. 22)
    - Pharmalab, Inc., BP 987 (Box 32, f. 1)
    - Phelps Co., BP 576 (Box 32, f. 2)
    - Philip Morris, Inc., 4-372-045 (Box 32, f. 3)
    - Phonograph Industry, note on, BP 642 (Box 32, f. 4)
    - Piper Aircraft Corporation, BP 934 (Box 32, f. 5)
    - Polaroid-Kodak, 4-376-266 (Box 32, f. 6)
    - Porter Manufacturing Co., IM 1453 (Box 32, f. 7)
    - Portland Cement in the U.K., GM 52r1, IMEDE (Box 32, f. 8)
    - Portland Co., BP 574 (Box 32, f. 9)
    - Potter Drug and Chemical Co., BP 433 (Box 32, f. 10)
    - Potter Manufacturing Co., BP 872 (Box 32, f. 11)
    - Prelude Corporation, 6-373-052 (Box 32, f. 12)
    - Prescription Drug Industry, part I, BP 956 (Box 32, f. 13)
    - Prescription Drug Industry, part II, BP 957 (Box 33, f. 1)
    - Press Equipment Corporation, BP 445r (Box 33, f. 2)
    - Private Government and the Corporate Conscience, BP 776 (Box 33, f. 3)
    - Raleigh Industries of America, 4-375-068 (Box 33, f. 4)
    - Rayburn Machinery Corporation, BP 384 (Box 33, f. 5)
    - The Real Paper, Inc. (A), 4-375-249 (Box 33, f. 6-7)
    - Recreational Vehicle Industry, 4-374-067 (Box 33, f. 8)
    - Robert Reilly (A) (B), BP 770 and BP 771 (Box 33, f. 9)
    - Relationship between “Formal” and “Informal” Organization, BP 684 (Box 33, f. 10)
    - Research, Inc., BP 673 (Box 33, f. 11)
    - Richardson Corporation, BP 955 (Box 34, f. 1)
    - Ripton Co., HP 190 (Box 34, f. 2)
    - Robbins, Inc., BP 849 (Box 34, f. 3)
    - Robert F. Kennedy High School, 9-474-183 (Box 34, f. 4)
    - Royal Shoe Co., BP 282 (Box 34, f. 5)
    - Royal-McBee Corporation (A), BP 691 (Box 34, f. 6)
    - Royal-McBee Corporation (Ar), BP 726 (Box 34, f. 7)
    - Royal-McBee Corporation (B), BP 692 (Box 34, f. 8)
    - Rugby Portland Cement, Ltd., GM 20, 56r2, IMEDE (Box 34, f. 9-12)
    - Rugby Portland Cement, Ltd., GM 57, IMEDE (Box 34, f. 13)
    - Sandusky Stove Co., BP 413 (Box 35, f. 1)
    - Sawyer and Ward, Inc., BP 563 (Box 35, f. 2)
    - Scott Bader Co., Ltd. (Box 35, f. 3-4)
    - Scripto, Inc., 4-374-343 (Box 35, f. 5)
    - Sears, Roebuck, and Co., 373-010 (Box 35, f. 6)
    - The Seiton Family, HP 217 (Box 35, f. 7)
    - Select Brushes, Inc., BP 663 (Box 35, f. 8)
    - Seven-Up Co. (A), 1-378-097 (Box 35, f. 9-10)
    - Seven-Up Co. (A), 1-378-097 (Box 36, f. 1)
    - Seven-Up Co. (B), 1-378-098 (Box 36, f. 2)
    - Sheldon Foundries, BP 588 (Box 36, f. 3)
    - Smith, Alexander, and Sons, Carpet Co., BP 439 (Box 36, f. 4)
    - Smith, Kline, and French Laboratories, BP 806 (Box 36, f. 5)
    - Smith-Corona-Marchant, Inc. (A), BP 698 (Box 36, f. 6)
    - Smith-Corona-Marchant, Inc. (Ar), BP 727 (Box 36, f. 7)
    - Smith-Corona-Marchant, Inc. (B), BP 699 (Box 36, f. 8)
    - Smith-Corona-Marchant, Inc. (Br), BP 728 (Box 36, f. 9)
    - Smith-Lansing Corporation, BP 816 (Box 36, f. 10)
    - Snowcroft Baking Co., BP 340 (Box 36, f. 11)
    - “The Social Responsibility of Business Is to Increase Its Profits,” by Milton Friedman, AMP 320 (Box 36, f. 12)
    - Solartron Electronic Group (A), GM 9, IMEDE (Box 36, f. 13)
    - Solartron Electronic Group, part II, GM 10, IMEDE (Box 37, f. 1)
    - Stacy Tile Co., BP 353 (Box 37, f. 2)
    - “Stages of Corporate Development: a Descriptive Model,” by B. Scott (Box 37, f. 3)
    - Stanton, J.W., Ltd. (A), GM 102, IMEDE (Box 37, f. 4-5)
    - Stanton, J.W., Ltd. (B), GM 103, IMEDE (Box 37, f. 6)
    - Stanwood, R.S., Co., BP 440 (Box 37, f. 7)
    - Strategy with a Grain of Salt, BP 739 (Box 37, f. 8)
    - Stratford Co., BP 443 (Box 37, f. 9)
    - Studebaker Corporation, BP 482 (Box 37, f. 10)
    - Sturm, Ruger, and Co., 4-375-114 (Box 37, f. 11)
    - Superb Biscuits, Inc., BP 585 (Box 37, f. 12)
    - Superior Separator Co., BP 450 (Box 37, f. 13)
    - Supreme Markets, Inc., BP 572 (Box 37, f. 14)
    - Sussex Oil Co., EA-A 1 (Box 38, f. 1)
    - Swift, Cleary, and Co. (A), BP 724 (Box 38, f. 2)
    - Swift, Cleary, and Co. (Ar), BP 724r (Box 38, f. 3)
    - Swift, Cleary, and Co. (B), BP 725 (Box 38, f. 4)
    - Swift, Cleary, and Co. (Br), BP 725r (Box 38, f. 5)
    - Tappan Co., 4-372-159 (Box 38, f. 6)
    - Tax Man, Inc., BP 973 (Box 38, f. 7)
    - Tennessee Coal and Iron (A), BP 793 (Box 38, f. 8)
    - Tennessee Coal and Iron (B), BP 794 (Box 38, f. 9)
    - Tensor Corporation, BP 947 (Box 38, f. 10)
    - Texas Corporation, BP 284 (Box 38, f. 11)
    - Texas Instruments (A), condensed, BP 901 (Box 38, f. 12)
    - Texas Instruments (B), GM 22, IMEDE (Box 39, f. 1)
    - Textron, Inc. (A), BP 912 (Box 39, f. 2)
    - Textron, Inc. (B), BP 913 (Box 39, f. 3)
    - Textron, Inc. (A)(B), condensed, 9-373-337 (Box 39, f. 4)
    - Time Magazine, 4-373-091 (Box 39, f. 5)
    - The Tire Industry, BP 850 (Box 39, f. 6)
    - The Tire Industry, BP 890 (Box 39, f. 7)
    - The Tobacco Industry and the Surgeon General’s Report, BP 796 (Box 39, f. 8)
    - The Trucking Industry, BP 603 (Box 39, f. 9)
    - The Typewriter Industry (A), BP 689 (Box 39, f. 10)
    - The Typewriter Industry (B), BP 690 (Box 39, f. 11)
    - The Typewriter Industry, note on, BP 729 (Box 40, f. 1)
    - Ulmer Co., BP 1020 (Box 40, f. 2)
    - Underwood Olivetti (A), BP 694 (Box 40, f. 3)
    - Underwood Olivetti (Ar), BP 710 (Box 40, f. 4)
    - Underwood Olivetti (Br), BP 711 (Box 40, f. 5)
    - Underwood Olivetti (B), BP 695 (Box 40, f. 6)
    - Underwood Olivetti (C), BP 696 (Box 40, f. 7)
    - Underwood Olivetti (D), BP 697 (Box 40, f. 8)
    - Uniroyal, Inc., BP 892 (Box 40, f. 9)
    - U.S. Steel Corporation, BP 792 (Box 40, f. 10)
    - U.S. vs. John R. Park (Executive Exposure to Criminal Liability), 1-377-118 (Box 40, f. 11)
    - Vacuum Metals Corporation, BP 469 (Box 40, f. 12)
    - Vail Associates, Inc., 4-374-031 (Box 40, f. 13)
    - Vappi and Co., BP 1000 (Box 40, f. 14)
    - Varo Machine Co., IM 1362r (Box 41, f. 1)
    - Viking Air Compressor, Inc., 9-372-623 (Box 41, f. 2)
    - Vlasic Foods, Inc., BP 1005 (Box 41, f. 3)
    - Warrington Hosiery Machinery Corporation, BP 554 and BP 554s (Box 41, f. 4)
    - Watch Industry, BP 648r (Box 41, f. 5)
    - Watchmaking Industry of Switzerland, GM 6r2, IMEDE (Box 41, f. 6-7)
    - Wayland Co., BP 571 (Box 41, f. 8)
    - Weeks Co., BP 398 (Box 41, f. 9)
    - What Role for the Corporate Director? (A)(B), BP 981 (Box 41, f. 10)
    - Wilton Oil Equipment Co. (A), BP 456 (Box 41, f. 11)
    - Wilton Oil Equipment Co. (B), BP 457 (Box 42, f. 1)
    - Wilford Woodruff & Co., BP 365 (Box 42, f. 2)
    - Wilcox Textile Machinery Co., BP 438 (Box 42, f. 3)
    - William Mitchell, 2-368-028 (Box 42, f. 4)
    - Wine Industry (1961), 4-373-314 (Box 42, f. 5)
    - Wine Industry (1973), 4-373-315 (Box 42, f. 6)
    - Wine-related cases: Pleasant Valley Co., 4-373-313 (Box 42, f. 7)
    - Wine-related cases: Taylor Wine Co. (A)(B), 4-373-309 and 4-373-310 (Box 42, f. 8)
    - Wine-related cases: Taylor Wine Co. (C), 4-373-311 (Box 42, f. 9)
    - Wine-related cases: Great Western Producers, 4-373-312 (Box 42, f. 10)
    - Wolverine Milk Co., BP 361 (Box 42, f. 11)
    - Woodman Chair Co., BP 478 (Box 42, f. 12)
    - Woolworth Co., BP 434 (Box 42, f. 13)
    - Xerox Corporation (A)(B), 4-372-350 and 4-373-051 (Box 42, f. 14)
    - Xerox Corporation (C), BP 838 (Box 42, f. 15)
    - Xerox, Special Service Leave Program, 4-373-051 (Box 43, f. 1)
    - Zebra National Bank, EA-A 19 (Box 43, f. 2)
  - Subseries B. Business Policy Teaching Files, 1948-1990
    This subseries consists of cases annotated by Christensen in preparation for their use in the classroom at HBS. Many case files contain supplementary teaching notes and supporting materials in addition to the printed or mimeographed cases themselves. Subseries B materials are similar to Subseries A, Annotated Cases, circa 1948-1990, but were maintained separately by Christensen. Therefore, they have been kept as a separate subseries within the collection.
    - Acoustic Research, Inc. (D), BP 830r (Box 43, f. 3)
    - Aerosol Techniques, Inc., BP 853 (Box 43, f. 4)
    - American Broadcasting-Paramount Theaters, Inc., BP 589 (Box 43, f. 5)
    - American Motors Corporation, BP 765 (Box 43, f. 6)
    - American Motors Corporation (B), BP 840 (Box 43, f. 7)
    - American Motors Corporation (C), BP 861 (Box 43, f. 8)
    - American Motors Corporation (D), BP 880 (Box 43, f. 9)
    - Appleton Machine Co. (A), BP 730 (Box 43, f. 10)
    - Appleton Machine Co. (B), BP 731 (Box 43, f. 11)
    - Associated Petroleum, BP 900r (Box 43, f. 12)
    - Bard Co., BP 580 (Box 43, f. 13)
    - Basic Industries, BP 899r (Box 43, f. 14)
    - Bay State Abrasive Products Co. (B), BP 573 (Box 43, f. 15)
    - Biddle Printing Co., BP 752 (Box 43, f. 16)
    - Business Machines Corporation, BP 754 (Box 43, f. 17)
    - Case (J.I.) Co. (A), revised, BP 763r (Box 43, f. 18)
    - Colony Trucking Co., BP 604r (Box 43, f. 19)
    - Comparative Strategies of the Four Major Tire and Rubber Producers, BP 852 (Box 43, f. 20)
    - Consolidated Vultee Aircraft Corporation (B), revised, BP 427r-B (Box 44, f. 1)
    - Continental Watchmakers Co., BP 647 (Box 44, f. 2)
    - Crown Cork and Steel Co., BP 800 (Box 44, f. 3)
    - Custom Packaging Co., BP 925 (Box 44, f. 4)
    - Deere and Co., BP 865 (Box 44, f. 5)
    - Dennison Manufacturing Co. (A), BP 896 (Box 44, f. 6)
    - Dennison Manufacturing Co. (B), BP 897 (Box 44, f. 7)
    - Dennison Manufacturing Co. (C), BP 898 (Box 44, f. 8)
    - Devonian Electronic Components, Ltd. (A)(B), GM 100-GM 101 (Box 44, f. 9)
    - Edwards, John, EA-A2 (Box 44, f. 10)
    - Farm Equipment Industry, BP 864 (Box 44, f. 11)
    - Firestone Tire and Rubber Co. (East-West Trade), BP 843 (Box 44, f. 12)
    - Florida Products, Ltd., BP 879 (Box 44, f. 13)
    - Galvor Co. - American Electric Viewpoint on Negotiating (B)-(E), BP 813A-BP 813D (Box 44, f. 14)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co., BP 891 (Box 44, f. 15)
    - Grangesberg (A1), revised, GM111r (Box 44, f. 16)
    - Grangesberg Group Presentation (May 1965) (Box 44, f. 17)
    - Hammond Tire and Rubber Co., BP 851 (Box 44, f. 18)
    - Head Ski Co., BP 888 (Box 45, f. 1)
    - Hilton Hotels Corporation (K1)(K5), BP 638 (Box 45, f. 2)
    - Indian Head Mills, Inc. (C), BP 500 (Box 45, f. 3)
    - Indian Head Mills, Inc., exam edition (1963) (Box 45, f. 4)
    - Instar Watch Co., BP 584 (Box 45, f. 5)
    - International Manufacturing Co. (B1), BP 780r1 (Box 45, f. 6)
    - International Manufacturing Co. series, teaching notes (Box 45, f. 7)
    - James Taylors, Inc., PBA 573r1, ICH 2 G17 (Box 45, f. 8)
    - Japanese Watch Industry as of 1959 (Box 45, f. 9)
    - Leadership in Industry, by Sir Halford Reddish (Box 45, f. 10)
    - Liebig’s Extract of Meat Co., GM 99 (Box 45, f. 11)
    - Life Insurance Companies, Private, note on, BP 637 (Box 45, f. 12)
    - Litton Industries, Inc. (Br), AMP 263 (Box 45, f. 13)
    - Litton Industries, Inc. (C), AMP 264 (Box 45, f. 14)
    - Management without Meddling, Ben Mills, BP 645 (Box 45, f. 15)
    - Massey-Ferguson, Ltd., BP 866 (Box 45, f. 16)
    - Mathatronics, Inc., BP 815 (Box 45, f. 17)
    - Merck and Co. (B), BP 494 (Box 45, f. 18)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (B3), BP 652 (Box 45, f. 19)
    - Midway Foods Corporation (C2), BP 870 (Box 45, f. 20)
    - Midway Foods Corporation, introduction, BP 662 (Box 45, f. 21)
    - My Years with General Motors, by Alfred P. Sloan, excerpts (Box 45, f. 22)
    - National Cereal Distributors, BP 522 (Box 45, f. 23)
    - NEFCO (B), BP 715 (Box 45, f. 24)
    - NEFCO (B1), BP 716 (Box 45, f. 25)
    - NEFCO (B3), BP 718 (Box 45, f. 26)
    - NEFCO (B4), BP 719 (Box 45, f. 27)
    - NEFCO (B5), BP 720 (Box 45, f. 28)
    - New York Times, BP 733 and 733s (Box 45, f. 29)
    - New York Times, revised, BP 733r (Box 46, f. 1)
    - No Margin for Failure, by C.M. Shanks (Box 46, f. 2)
    - Office Machine Industry, Note on, AMP 248 (Box 46, f. 3)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.pA. (A1)-(A4), AMP 224-227 (Box 46, f. 4)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.p.A. (B2), AMP 231 (Box 46, f. 5)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.p.A. (D), AMP 234 (Box 46, f. 6)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.pA. (E1), AMP 235 (Box 46, f. 7)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.p.A. (F1), AMP 237 (Box 46, f. 8)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.p.A. (F2)-(F4), AMP 238-AMP 240 (Box 46, f. 9)
    - Olivetti & Co., S.p.A., (H), AMP 247 (Box 46, f. 10)
    - Phonograph Industry, Note on, BP 642, ICH 5 G43 (Box 46, f. 11)
    - Pilgrim Life Insurance Co. (A), BP 484 (Box 46, f. 12)
    - Pilgrim Life Insurance Co. (B) (C), BP 485-BP 486 (Box 46, f. 13)
    - Planning in the Magazine Industry, BP 837 (Box 46, f. 14)
    - “The Problem of Relating Faith to Decisions Involves Compromise,” by Albert Rasmusson, BP 530 (Box 46, f. 15)
    - “Protestant Piety and the Right Wing,” by George Younger, BP 533 (Box 46, f. 16)
    - Relations of Economic Power Groups, Private and Public, BP 547 (Box 46, f. 17)
    - Relationship between “Formal” and “Informal” Organization, BP 684 (Box 46, f. 18)
    - Reliance Publishing Corporation, BP 836 (Box 46, f. 19)
    - Religion and Business Policy, BP 539 (Box 46, f. 20)
    - Religion and Business Policy (B), BP 540 (Box 46, f. 21)
    - Religion and Business Policy (C), BP 541 (Box 46, f. 22)
    - Research, Inc., BP 673 (Box 46, f. 23)
    - “Revised Sense of Values,” by E.D. Canham, excerpts, BP 644 (Box 46, f. 24)
    - Robbins, Inc., BP 849 (Box 46, f. 25)
    - Rugby Portland Cement Co. (A), GM 56r2, ICH 7G19 (Box 46, f. 26)
    - Rugby Portland Cement Co. (B), ICH 7G20 (Box 46, f. 27)
    - Rugby Portland Cement Co. (C), GM 16 (Box 46, f. 28)
    - Select Brushes, Inc., BP 663 (Box 46, f. 29)
    - Smith Kline & French Laboratories (Parnate), BP 806 (Box 46, f. 30)
    - Social Duties and Opportunities of the Business Organization, BP 615 (Box 46, f. 31)
    - Solartron Electronic Group, Ltd. (A), Parts I and II, ICH 4 G 98 (Box 46, f. 32)
    - Solartron Electronic Group, Ltd. (C), GM 82, ICH 9 G 1 (Box 46, f. 33)
    - Solartron Electronic Group, Ltd. (D), GM 83, ICH 9 G 76 (Box 47, f. 1)
    - Some Negative Thinking about Norman Vincent Peale, by W.L. Miller, BP 535 (Box 47, f. 2)